

CONTACT

- Bucharest, Romania
- secareanu.alexandru98
 @gmail.com
- github.com/apsecareanu
- secareanu-alexandrubb97921b8/
- +40 728 435 738

SKILLS SUMMARY

Programming Languages:

HTML/CSS, Javascript, SQL/NoSQL, PHP

Technologies/Frameworks:

ReactJS, NodeJS, EJS, ExpressJS, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Bootstrap, SASS

KNOWLEDGE AND CONCEPTS

- Mobile first responsive design concepts
- UI/UX
- RESTful API
- Git version control
- Unix Command Line

LANGUAGES

- English C1
- Romanian Native
- Polish A2

SECAREANU ALEXANDRU

WEB DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

My name is Alexandru, I am a Web Developer for 2+ years, with full-stack experience, covering the full development of a web application, from the front-end to the back-end. My main technologies for development are ReactJS for Front-End and NodeJS with ExpressJS for Back-End with MongoDB/Mongoose for databases. Certificates and diplomas regarding technical skills:

- Front-End Development Diploma
- Microsoft MTA HTML/CSS Certificate
- Microsoft MTA Javascript Certificate

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

Digital Star | January 2022 - Present

- Handling Front End Development of websites for Digital Star's clients by implementing the design received into HTML/SASS and creating the functionalities requested by the clients, such as quizzes, validations, animations, databases submissions for forms using JavaScript library ¡Query and PhP WordPress.
- Providing maintenance services for several clients, such as Ursus
 Breweries, Nescafe Dolce Gusto, BMW Dealers, Hochland, Mixa, Starbucks
 by implementing content, removing content, changing website
 stylesheets.
- Maintenance performed directly into code or into the CMS chosen by the client, such as Drupal, Magento or Wordpress.

Back-Up Technical Escalation Agent

Computer Generated Solution | July 2020 - February 2021

- Assisting Technical Support Agents with calls that were required escalation to a supervisor and any other inquiry.
- Assisting Sprint U.S. customers with delicate matters regarding their plans, invoices or technical related issues.

Quality Assurance Agent

Ubisoft Romania | March 2017 - June 2017

• Testing Ubisoft games in various stages of development and providing relevant feedback to the development team for improvements and fixes.



CONTACT

- Bucharest, Romania
- secareanu.alexandru9 8@gmail.com
- github.com/apsecareanu
- secareanu-alexandrubb97921b8/
- +40 728 435 738

SKILLS SUMMARY

Programming Languages:HTML/CSS, Javascript, SQL, PHP

Technologies/Frameworks:

ReactJS, NodeJS, EJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB, Mongoose, Bootstrap, SASS

KNOWLEDGE AND CONCEPTS

- Mobile first responsive design concepts
- UI/UX
- RESTful API
- Git version control
- Unix Command Line

LANGUAGES

- English C1
- Romanian Native
- Polish A2

COMPLETED PROJECTS

Several Biofarm projects (Anghirol, Extravalerianic)

- Presentation website for Biofarm products such as Anghirol and Extravalerianic.
- The projects have included full responsive design using Bootstrap and SASS, from desktop to tablet and mobile, a quiz for each website created with jQuery, with maintenance platform being Wordpress with ACF written in PhP.

Muller Campaigns for Kaffee, Rizo and Pezzi

- Campaign web pages for Muller Kaffee, Rizo and Pezzi.
- The campaigns were created with full responsive design using Bootstrap and SASS, written in PhP, with the form functionality being written with Javascript (jQuery), form submission being handled by AJAX, with validation by Javascript and PhP code. The database was handled in PhPMyAdmin.

Several maintenance projects for DigitalStar clients

- Maintenance provided by me to BMW Dealers, Hochland, Mixa, DespreAlcool, Ursus Breweries.
- Adding new sections to the mentioned websites, modifying or removing content, design changes, SEO modifications, implementing features or scripts (such as TagManager), handling newsletters logistics.

EDUCATION HISTORY

Videle Theoretical Highschool

Student between 2013 - 2017

- 4 Years of Highschool studies on a foreign languages profile with a C1 certificate in English.
- Graduated in 2017 with a Bacalaureat Diploma.

University of Bucharest - Faculty of Foreign Languages

Student between 2018 - 2021

- 3 years of studies on Applied Modern Languages profile with English and Polish.
- Several other courses taken, including Law, Info and Economics.

IT School

Front-End Development Course | March 2021 - Sep 2021 (100h of training and 200+ hours of individual work)

- Studied the Front-End Development, with the following skills acquired HTML/CSS, JavaScript, React.
- Graduated the course with a certificate for Web Development from the Ministry of Education as well as two Microsoft Certificates.